1985 - Wish You Were Here!
Ping Pong Summer is a comedy, drama, history film directed by Michael Tully.
In 1985 a summer vacation in Ocean City, Md., changes the life of a shy
white teen who's obsessed with table tennis and hip-hop music.
Rad Miracle, played by Marcello Conte.
Michelle Miracle, played by Helena May Seabrook.
Mr. Miracle, played by John Hannah.
Mrs. Miracle, played by Lea Thompson.
Stacy Summers, played by Emmi Shockley.
Lyle Ace, played by Joseph McCaughtry.
Ping Pong Summer is a 2014 American independent coming-of-age
comedy film written and directed by Michael Tully.
The film had its world premiere at 2014 Sundance
Film Festival on January 18, 2014.
Gravitas Ventures acquired the distribution rights of the film; they released
the film theatrically and by video on demand on June 6, 2014.
Millennium Entertainment handled the home release of the film.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.